Hey everyone, I was,
working on Claude Code quite a bit,
these days and I found a couple of,
I will say gaps, or not gaps,
basically the way of, I work, I felt like I could have added,
those things into a terminal that would have helped my day-to-day life.
So, I just tried to create, an, a terminal application called Zede,
what it basically does is, it's kind of a Arc-styled,
terminal, where you can, pin any,
you can pin any tab, any terminal,
next time when you close and when you open,
it, it keeps of that particular,
pinned tab. Then also,
so this, this is the interface of it, where you can either open,
so from this new Claude, new tab,
you can actually open a Claude Code or,
a shell. You can also load any of the previously saved,
interfaces, which it can, it will,
It also gives you, like, you can compact the previous context and start a
new conversation with this. There are different spaces, like, you know, you can create
your personal space, office space,
and, it all gets saved. So there is a separation of,
thing. Apart from that,
this is our main, tab. Terminal window, I also have this Claude
context, thing, which basically exposes a lot of things that Claude has internally,
like, you know, skills, plugins, most of these,
we hardly even know, like, we have a conversation in Claude,
Claude tries to basically,
you know, say part of,
those conversations into maybe facts,
decisions, preferences, to-dos,
and next time when we are, typing something,
our, output is basically, the output is basically impacted by all
these things that Claude already stores, like,
there are 1,273 facts,
it has stored, right, and, we have hardly any idea,
like, you know what these are like, there are different.
These many to-dos, all these are basically internally what Claude has stored,
I, another thing that I feel problematic with me is, these prompts, so, when,
when, when
I want to navigate back to the previous conversation and.
It's very difficult, like, you know, between those,
long chat, it's very hard to find your own chat,
so this prompt basically, can give you option where you can click on any
prompt and it can scroll you back to the previous prompt, it's a demo
time now, I will give you a quick demo of things.
Now, let's say, like, I have added a couple of prompts here.
so, what it will also do is, it, whatever our last prompt is,
it will just add that summary over here in this tab for easy recognition,
then, we can simply save this conversation,
let's say, like, Zede walkthrough,
Thanks for watching! So,
it, it saves, this entire conversation into JSON,
like, mostly Human Readable, it is already there in Claude Code,
but, it's not very easy to navigate those,
saved memories, but, with this, we can just save it to,
and next time, when we want, we can just,
load a conversation in a new session, and,
it all starts from there. Apart from that,
discovering and editing skills, you can, let's say, like, I have a Humanizer skill,
which can basically, something, Claude Code, Open Code, and then, let's say,
I want to edit this,
I can simply go and, remove this,
okay. And I
can simply save it from here, so, it also makes,
the edit, managing of, skills, plugins, all this very easy, front,
easy to discover, and,
there are keyboard shortcuts like Command M,
this will close that side panel from right,
and, you can,
this, this panel can be closed, so, this gives you, distraction free space,
we also have settings where, you get to choose what thing you want,
and what, where the sync functionality
is not yet working,
I need to switch it and more time feeding on this,
yes, so, this is all it is,
I think, yep, you can also forget certain things like,
you know, you can just forget some to-dos and,
in case you recently forgotten something,
you, you can find it over here, that way you can also clean up
your, Claude coding memory and internals.
So, I think that's pretty much it,
hope this helps everyone. Thank you.